freeconference.com 2015-03-15

# Privacy: Protecting customer privacy during telephone conferencing is of highest importance. Contact us about our teleconferencing services today!

FreeConference.com has a long-standing policy of protecting customer privacy.  We believe that you have the right to know whatinformation we collect from you as well as how that information is used, disclosed and protected.  We have created this policy statement (the "Policy") to explain our privacy practices and policies.  When you use any FreeConference.com product or service, you should understand when and how personal information is collected, used, disclosed and protected.

We will not sell or disclose information to third parties without your consent or as otherwise provided in this Policy.  You should know, however, that when you sign up or use any of our products or services we may use information about who you are, where and when you browse on our Web site and how you use our network, or other information as described in this Policy.  We do this in order to provide you with better service and to enrich your user experience.  Whenever our systems and the technology permit we will allow you to limit such use.

FreeConference.com will revise and update this Policy if our practices change or as we add new services or change existing ones.  We will also modify this policy if we find better ways to inform you of products we think will be of interest.  You should refer back to this page for the latest information.

The following points provide you with an overview of our policies and a link to the full detail about our privacy practices.  We also provide you several ways to communicate with us if you have any questions about this Policy.

 **Does FreeConference.com Collect Personal Information About Me?**   Yes, FreeConference.com collects personal information about you so that we can deliver products or services you request.  This happens automatically when you interact with us, such as when you log into the service.  Sometimes, FreeConference.com buys commercially available marketing and sales information from third parties so we can better serve you. Tell me more.

 **Does FreeConference.com Collect Information on Children Under the Age of 13?** FreeConference.com does not knowingly, directly or passively, collect information from children under the age of 13.  If we create offers and products that make it appropriate to collect information from children under the age of 13, we will notify you of the change in this Policy.  We also will ask a parent to confirm his/her consent in advance of any collection, use or disclosure of that information.  Tell me more.

 **How Does FreeConference.com Use Personal Information?** We use personal information to provide services or complete transactions you have requested and to anticipate and resolve problems with your services.  We may also use this information to create and inform you of products or services from FreeConference.com or others that may better meet your needs.  Tell me more.

 **When Does FreeConference.com Disclose Personal Information?** We do not sell personal information to third parties.  We will disclose personal information to third parties when we have your consent to do so, such as to complete a transaction you have requested, or as part of the terms and conditions for a particular service.  We also may disclose personal information to third parties to protect the rights and property of the company or its subscribers. Tell me more.

 **Does FreeConference.com Use Cookies?** Yes, FreeConference.com uses cookies for a variety of reasons, including improving your browsing experience online.  In addition, cookies help us personalize the site experience for you. Tell me more.

 **What is your policy for providing refunds for purchases?**   If you use our conference service we will bill your credit card for each minute spent on the line by each caller who calls into the conference.  If you request a refund, our policy is to research all refund claims no later than the first full business day following your inquiry.  If we find that an adjustment is fairly justified, we will process that adjustment or credit within five business days of the original inquiry.  If the adjustment or credit is not deemed to be valid, we will provide a written explanation within the same time frame.

 **Does FreeConference.com Place Banner Ads on Other Web Sites?**   FreeConference.com currently uses a third-party advertising company to place our ads on the Internet and cookie technology is used to measure the effectiveness of those ads.  You should know that the use of such cookies is subject to the third party's privacy policy, and not the policy of FreeConference.com. Tell me more.

 **How Secure Is Information About Me?** We maintain a variety of physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards to guard your personal information.  Tell me more.

 **Can I Check Account Information for Accuracy?** Through our web site, you can change or review account information.

 **Will This Policy Be Updated?** FreeConference.com expects to update this Policy periodically.   You should refer back to this page often for the latest information and the effective date of any changes to the Policy.

 **To Whom Should I Direct Privacy Questions or Concerns?** You have several ways to contact us about questions to this policy and about your services. Tell me more.

 **Information Collected About You.   ** We collect a variety of personal information about users of our products or services.  Personal information is information that can be directly associated with a specific person or entity such as a customer's name, address, telephone number, e-mail address, or information about activities that is directly linked to that person (for example, IP address information).

FreeConference.com recognizes that parents often sign up for our products and services for family use, including for use by minors.  Any information collected from such usage will appear to be the personal information of the actual subscriber to the service, and will be treated as such under this Policy.  Furthermore, FreeConference.com does not knowingly, directly or passively, collect information from children under the age of 13.  If we create offers and products that make it appropriate to collect information from children under the age of 13, we will notify you of the change in this Policy.  We also will ask a parent to confirm his/her consent in advance of any collection, use or disclosure of that information.

When our customer is a business or other entity purchasing service for employees or other authorized users, this Policy will generally govern the personal information associated with individual employees or authorized users.  However, whether the business customer has access to personal information of employees or other authorized users will be governed by the terms of any service agreement.  So, employees or other authorized users should check with the business customer regarding its privacy practices.

Our definition of personal information does not include "aggregate" information.  Aggregate information is data we collect about a group or category of services or customers from which individual customer identities have been removed.  In other words, how you use a service may be collected and combined with information about how others use the same service, but no personal information will be included in the resulting data.  Aggregate data helps us understand trends and customer needs so that we can better consider new services or tailor existing services to customer desires.  An example of aggregate data is our ability to prepare a report that indicates that a certain number of our customers always use our conferencing services at a certain time of day.  The report would not contain any personal information but the aggregate data might be purchased by or shared with a third party.

Here are the types of personal and other information we collect.  You should refer to the rest of this Policy to see how we use, disclose and protect that information: 

  * Information You Give Us:  We collect information you give us when you sign up with FreeConference.com or use our services.  For example, you may provide us an e-mail address when signing up for service.  You might not have thought about it this way, but the e-mail address you use when browsing to our web site is an example of information you give us and that we collect and use.
  * Automatically Collected Information:  We automatically receive certain types of information whenever you interact with us.  For example, when you visit the FreeConference.com Web site, our systems automatically collect your IP address and the type and version of browser you use.
  * Information from Other Sources:  We may obtain information about you from outside sources and add it to or combine it with our account information.  We may use commercially available demographic and marketing information from third parties to help us better serve you or inform you about new products or services that we think will be of interest to you.

Back to Top

 **Children's Online Privacy Protection Act.**

FreeConference.com does not knowingly, directly or passively, collect information from children under the age of 13.  If we create offers and products that make it appropriate to collect information from children under the age of 13, we will notify you of the change in this Policy.  We also will ask a parent to confirm his/her consent in advance of any collection, use or disclosure of that information.  You should be aware, however, that web browsers and conferencing services set up for family use may be used by minors without the knowledge of FreeConference.com.  If that happens, any information collected from the usage will appear to be the personal information of the actual adult subscriber and treated as such under this Policy. Back to Top

 **Use of Personal Information.**

 **Internal Use**.  In general, we use personal information to serve our customers, to enhance and extend our customer relationship, and so our customers can take maximum advantage of our products and services.  For example, by understanding how you use our Web site from your computer, we are able to customize and personalize your experience.  More specifically, we use personal information to provide services or complete transactions you have requested, to anticipate and resolve problems with your services, and to create and inform you of products or services from FreeConference.com or others that better meet your needs.  FreeConference.com may use e-mail to inform you about new products or services we think will interest you.

 **Third Party Use**.   You should review the following section to understand when FreeConference.com discloses personal information to third parties. Back to Top

 **Disclosure of Personal Information.**   Information about our customers is one of our most important business assets, and therefore we strive to protect it and keep it confidential.  We do not sell personal information to third parties without your consent.  When and what types of information FreeConference.com discloses depends on the teleconferencing services and in some cases the choices you have made.  We disclose personal information as follows:  Your Consent.  FreeConference.com will not disclose personal information other than in accordance with this Policy.  In general, that means that you must consent to the disclosure in advance.  Depending on the service, we may obtain your consent in a number of ways, including:

  * In writing;
  * Verbally;
  * Online by clicking a button;
  * At the time of service initiation when your consent is part of the required terms and conditions to use the service.

For example, your consent to disclose personal information can be implied simply by the nature of your request, such as when you ask us to deliver an e-mail to another person.  Your return address is disclosed as part of the service and your consent to do so implied by your use of the service.  To determine how personal information may be disclosed as part of a particular service, you should review the terms and conditions of use for that service.

We may share personal information with third parties as necessary to complete a transaction, perform a service on our behalf or that you have requested or to enhance our ability to serve you better.  When the third party acts solely on our behalf, FreeConference.com will require them to follow our privacy practices. 

**Business Transfers:** Information about our customers, including personal information, will be disclosed as part of any merger, sale of the company assets or acquisition as well as in the unlikely event of an insolvency, bankruptcy or receivership in which personal information would be transferred as one of the business assets of the company.

 **Protection of FreeConference.com and Others:**   We release personal information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law (e.g., a lawful subpoena, E911 information); to enforce or apply our customer agreements; to initiate, render, bill, and collect for services; to protect our rights or property, or to protect users of those services and other carriers from fraudulent, abusive, or unlawful use of, or subscription to, such services. Back to Top

 **FreeConference.com Use of "Cookies"** Cookies are small text files placed on your hard drive by a Web site when you visit.  These files identify your computer and records your preferences and other data about your visit so that when you return to the site, the site knows who you are and can personalize your visit.  For example, cookies enable a Web site function so that you only have to log in once.

In general, we use cookies to personalize the site and make recommendations based on selections you have made in the past as well as to improve the site experience; and to complete transactions you have requested.  Advertisers that serve ads on our site may also use their own cookies.  Such outside cookies are governed by the privacy policies of the entities placing the ads, and are not subject to this Policy.

As technology advances and cookies provide more functionality, we expect to utilize them in different offerings in different ways.  As we do so, this Policy will be updated to provide you with more information.  Back to Top

 **FreeConference.com placement of Banner Ads on other Web Sites.**   FreeConference.com may use third-party advertising companies to place advertisements about our products and services on other Web sites.  These third-party companies may use other technology such as Web beacons or tagging, to measure the effectiveness of our ads.  To measure advertising effectiveness and offer selective ad content, they may use anonymous information about your visits to our and other Web sites.  But in all cases, they use an anonymous number to identify you, and do NOT use your name, address, phone number, e-mail address, or anything that personally identifies you.  The use of such cookies is subject to their privacy policy, not the policy of FreeConference.com. Back to Top

 **Network and Information Security** We maintain a variety of physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards to guard your personal information.  For example, we use accepted tools and techniques to protect against unauthorized access to our systems.  Also, we restrict access to personal information about you to those employees who need to know that information to provide products or services to you.  You should be aware that FreeConference.com has no control over the security of other sites on the Internet you might visit, interact with, or from which you buy products or services. 

An important part of protecting the security of personal information is your efforts to protect against unauthorized access to your user name and password and to your computer.  Also, be sure to sign off when finished using a shared computer and always log out of any site when viewing personal account information.  Back to Top

 **Updating this Policy.   ** FreeConference.com will revise or update this Policy if our practices change, as we change existing or add new services or as we develop better ways to inform you of products we think will be of interest.  You should refer back to this page often for the latest information and the effective date of any changes. Back to Top

 **Contact Us**   FreeConference.com is committed to the policies set forth in this Policy.  If you have any questions, comments or concerns about this Policy, please contact [privacy@freeconference.com](mailto:privacy@freeconference.com).   Or you can send us mail to: FreeConference.com, Attn: Privacy, P.O. Box 23, Glendale CA 91209.  Effective Date:  January 1, 2009. Back to Top

 **Opt Out:** If you wish to opt out from all future correspondence from us, please click here.
